{
    "id": "b3c47cdcbc33442582b7790f611bc361",
    "title": "Relative Pronouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Jane with .......................... I traveled to Delhi is a nice girl.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the hotel ........................ our meetings used to take place.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "where",
                "there",
                "here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The apples ............................. I bought yesterday were good.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the girl ......................... won the first prize.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "which",
                "whom"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the house ......................... my father bought last year.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "which",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "................................... people lived here in the 1950â€™s, the cost of living was low.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Where",
                "When",
                "Then"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The washing machine .......................... I bought yesterday was not very expensive.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "what",
                "who"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The traveler ......................... I met on the way was a well-read person.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "whom",
                "which",
                "what"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I saw a girl ........................ beauty took my breath away.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "her",
                "who",
                "who's",
                "whose"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "He has written a novel .......................... name I have forgotten.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "whose",
                "who's",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}